{
    "id": "0fca1efa52e24a44b580a257cf1078bd",
    "title": "Progressive and Non-progressive Uses of Verbs Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "27cf6fc19186449ea70c03ef76dc7097",
            "title": "Progressive and Non-progressive Uses of Verbs",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I ....................... fine.",
                    "description": "The word feel can be used in continuous and non-continuous forms to talk about health. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "feel",
                        "am feeling",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ........................ you shouldn't do this.",
                    "description": "When feel means 'have an opinion', it is not used in the continuous form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "feel",
                        "am feeling",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "What ..................... you ..................... about my hair style?",
                    "description": "When think means 'have an opinion' it doesn't have an ing form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "do, think",
                        "are, thinking",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ............................. your dad tomorrow.",
                    "description": "We use the present continuous to talk about an arrangement that already exists. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "see",
                        "am seeing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The fish ......................... awful.",
                    "description": "Verbs that refer to the use of the senses do not normally have continuous forms. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "smells",
                        "is smelling",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ......................... this song.",
                    "description": "The verbs love and like are almost never used in the continuous form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "like",
                        "am liking",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I rang her up because I ........................... to talk.",
                    "description": "The verb want is not normally used in the continuous form. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "wanted",
                        "was wanting",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ....................... what you mean.",
                    "description": "When 'see' means understand it is not used in the continuous form. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "see",
                        "am seeing",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The stew ............................ wonderful.",
                    "description": "The verb 'taste' is not normally used in the continuous form. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "tastes",
                        "is tasting",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "If I ....................... the answer, I will tell you.",
                    "description": "The verb 'know' is not normally used in the continuous form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "am knowing",
                        "know",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ............................ 85 kg.",
                    "description": "The verb 'weigh' is not normally used in the continuous form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "is weighing",
                        "weighs",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "..................... you .................... in God?",
                    "description": "The verb 'believe' does not normally have a continuous form. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Do, believe",
                        "Are, believing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}